http://www.enzymedica.com/pages/privacy-policy

Skip to content
FREE GIFT and FREE SHIPPING over $50!
ATPro
Breaks down fat, fiber, protein & carbs* Speeds up digestion* Boosts energy* Reduces occasional...
ATPro
Breaks down fat, fiber, protein & carbs* Speeds up digestion* Boosts energy* Reduces occasional...
Apple Cider Vinegar
Healthy weight loss* Contains the Mother for maximum benefit 10 to 20 real apples...
GlutenEase™
Supports gluten and casein intolerance* Includes additional enzymes to help digest the entire meal*...
Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Shop Products
Choose your FREE gift:
Orders greater than $50 qualify for a free gift.
I don’t want this
Taxes:
- -
Shipping:
Free
Subtotal:
$ 0.00
Checkout
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.enzymedica.com.
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
Enzymedica may also collect your email address for marketing purposes, should you choose to provide it. If you volunteer your email address, we refer to this action as "Opting in". By opting in, Enzymedica uses this information to send you certain materials such as special offers, discounts, promotions, blog articles, company news, recipes, product announcements, or other content related to our business that may interest you.
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking about Device Information, Order Information, and Email Address.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).
Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. This helps us to make site improvements and optimizations, allowing for a better overall experience -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at request@enzymedica.com or by mail using the details provided below:
771 Commerce Dr, Venice, FL, 34292, United States
941-505-5565
Powered By Discount Ninja
×
[[BODY]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1_LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2_LABEL]]
×
[[HEADER]]
[[MINIMIZED]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[TEXT]]
×
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[TEXT]]
[[HEADER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[BODY]]
[[QUANTITY_LABEL]]
[[PRICE_LABEL]]
[[TIER_ROW]]
[[PRICE]]
[[LABEL]]
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ROW]]
